Hey everyone welcome and welcome Zappel! Hi! Because I have a guest today and it's going to be a very very
experimental video today because she brought an outfit for me. I did! A cosplay outfit. It's gonna be so cute!
cute. I have no idea what's going to happen and what kind of outfit it is. We
met last year at a photoshoot and I saw that you like doing these kind of cute
cosplay outfits. How would you describe your cosplay style? It's a bit hard
because it's very just cutesy, maybe a bit e-girl, just some outfits I like. Yeah
and I also post some sets on Patreon some of the time. Yeah I will put it in the
description text so check her out and now I guess you have to show me what's
going to happen now
alright okay I I mean I I love your cosplays they're really cute but I don't
know this looks like a really lot of fur is this the color the right do I carry the right one
I still change it but I don't know. I think it would suit you actually.
It's not your thing. Maybe.
Let's unpack them. Okay.
So the tail? Yeah.
So. I don't know if you ever played Pokemon. I did.
I was so proud when I could like buy myself the yellow edition when it released all these years ago.
Oh yes, I'm old. So I did play the game for my edition.
Because those are Eevee evolutions in cute little suits.
Everyone, look closely at this collar. It's up. Up!
Okay. I mean, they're super cozy. And they have tails. Yes.
And paws. And paws? Okay.
Like in my outfits I most of the time just pick a fitting wig or something but sometimes
the hair color just fits so...
Okay, so I don't have to wear a wig or should I wear a wig?
If you want to, I brought some too.
You can also...
I will do whatever you want.
Alright.
Wanna try it out?
Yeah, let's get changed.
Pokeball go!
I don't see anything with the wig.
That doesn't matter. You look cute. That's everything.
Also I can't do anything anymore with these paws.
So?
Very cute.
Oh my god.
You just hit me with your... what's it? Ears?
Or the snake?
It's ears.
Yeah.
You wanna see yourself?
Yes, I wanna see myself.
The paws!
It looks like a Christmas outfit!
A tiny bit, right?
It's like the Sesame Street character.
Like Cookie Monster.
Ew!
Paws!
Not very practical, yes.
Not picture at all, it's like...
This wig...
Oh no! Oh no!
Yes, you wanted a cute cosplay outfit and that's like...
the cutest, most cosplay outfit I could think of.
Show your tail.
The he- oh, my tail.
Your tail.
And these... whatever these are.
Oh my god, that tail is awesome.
I'm not so sure about...
What are these?
Are these ears?
You're a water pokemon, Vaporeon.
Obviously I'm a water pokemon.
What's it called?
So, Vaporeon.
Vaporeon.
And I'm Sylveon.
I think.
Espeon?
Is it Espeon?
Oh.
I mean these paws are padded like they're soft.
Maybe?
Yeah and the what's it called?
Krallen claws.
The claws are like PVC which is kind of cute but like they're so so unpractical.
No selfies today.
I mean they do have like these zippers so I could cheat and...
Will you manage?
I don't know.
No it's stuck!
Oh no!
Wait.
I can try to escape too.
Oh god.
You can put the hand outside.
I can try to escape too. Oh god.
Oh my god.
It's so warm. It's really warm. Also like we could also like...
Oh yeah you could just take the sleeves off. Take the sleeves off, then it's the summer version.
with a very fuzzy hood yeah and fuzzy wig and tail yeah but like the wig is always in your face
it doesn't matter how it sits is this like how you would go to a convention no that's more why not
bit impractical like for conventions i do more casual cosplays not casual but more
known characters like I have a Loki cosplay I did Flora from Winx Club and
Princess Bubblegum but for Patreon it's just cutesy things. Cutesy okay.
Fluffy paws tails ears there's a lot of that. I have a co-op. Yeah! I still can't with the headpiece. It's beautiful.
Looks like I have an elephant on my head.
No!
Anyway, we're super serious here.
Serious business.
I honestly think it's cute.
It's not at all what I would have expected.
Like, at all.
What would you have wished for?
I have no idea since I'm not really into cosplays or since a lot of pop culture is like, what?
So, at least it's not a superhero. I'm really glad for that.
And I mean it's cozy and warm and fuzzy. That's kind of cute.
So yeah. And I can live with Pokemon because Pokemon are awesome.
So yeah.
Thanks for this. I really had a lot of fun.
Thank you for trusting me.
Yeah, well, what else do I...
What have I done?
Anyway, I will get my revenge in the video which I'm going to dress you
If you want to see more of her check out her patreon and Instagram. I will link everything in the description
And yeah
I'll see you in the next video. I hope you liked this one. Tell me in the comments. Are you into cosplay?
How do you like these cosplays?
what did you think of this experiment? Have a nice day and we'll see you around. Bye!